

# ALHIMNY DWINATA UTAMA IT DEVELOPMENT, ANALYST, AND SUPPORT

- A +62-878-2535-1290
- alhimnydu.github.io/portofolio
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/alhimnydwinata-utama-490b9420a/

#### **RELEVANT SKILLS**

- Programming
  - o PHP (CI / Laravel)
  - Python (Flask)
  - o C# (ASP.NET)
  - Java (Android Studio)
  - SQLServer
  - MySQL
  - MongoDB
- Support
  - Set Up Network , Email
     Software and Hardware.
  - Deploy Website on Hosting (CI/CD)
- Additional
  - Understand GIT (Github / Gitlab)
  - Editing Video and Photo

#### SUMMARY

Hello I am Alhimny, I have work experience as a developer software PHP, ASP.NET, and Python. I created some system for company engaged in finance and education. I am also interest in Machine Learning and Deep Learning and created ML or DL system with framework Flask Python. See my portofolio at link alhimny.herokuapp.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



Xtremax Teknologi Indonesia Associate Software Development - Backend January 2023 - Present



Dana Pensiun Astra, Astra International Information Technology Development & System Analyst January 2022 - Desember 2022



Institut Teknologi Nasional (ITENAS) Full-stack Developer March 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 9 months)

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**



## **Bachelor of Computer Science**

Institution: Institut Teknologi Nasional

Bandung

Year of Graduation: 2021 Cum Laude, GPA 3.86 Scholarship

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



### **Data Science**

Institution: Sanbercode 2021



# **Sertification Android Digital Talent**

Institution: Digital Talent & Dicoding

2019